

Raul Gongora

+46 70-4264615

raul@dulcecare.se

Languagues:

Spanish - Native

English – Fluently

Swedish - Fluently

Russian - Fluently

SUMMARY:

Senior IT Administrator with large experience in both Windows and Unix-Linux Administration but also in RDBMS. Several years of work experience in telecom and hotel branches as System Administrator/IT specialist for business-critical IT systems with high demands on availability and IT security. Having refreshed my knowledge with new technologies, specially in Python programming language during the last year, am I prepared to take new challenges in my next employment.

WORK EXPERIENCE:

Work at my own company,

August 2019 - January 2022

Taking control of my own company Dulcecare AB, not only allowed me to develop leadership and management skills, but also to interact directly with employees, thus helping me to make important decisions in the areas of finance and human resources while I was able to acquire a holistic view of the company's overall performance. During this period of time have I managed to reorganized the company and decide its future development.

System Administrator, Tele2

May 2001 - August 2019

As a System Administrator for the second larger Telecom company in Sweden I belonged to the IT department and network management team with the responsability for maintanance, design, monitoring and security of alarm suerveillance system for the whole company infrastructure. The work went in a complex environment mainly Windows and different Linux flavors so integration of these systems was part of my admins tasks. In addition, I gained experience working with different Databases such as Oracle, Sql, Sybase etc. The last project I was involved consisted of migration of our main workbench application to the virtual environment(VMWARE) and cloud platform.

System Administrator, Radisson Hotels August 1996 - April 2001

Management, monitoring, support, upgrades, backup & recovery strategies for the whole company IT infrastructure and IT systems(e-mail, AD, Remote Access, Corporate Internet and Intranet, Booking, Telephony and Economy Systems). First line support for internal users and cooperate with customers and external suppliers. Corporate network configuration and troubleshooting(Cisco routers, switches, firewall) as well as the security of the company's wide and local area networks.

During the period I worked at Radisson SAS, happened the integration of different Hotels within the same chain into a central IT organization. This was a large project with a huge financial impact for the company. As a result of this integration I was involved in the implementation of new technologies as Terminal Server, Citrix Metaframe for uses access to the central managed Data Center.

TRAINING:

Master of Science in Mathematics, In the State University of Moldova August 1985 - July 1990

PERSONALLY:

As a person, I see myself as service minded, flexible, open to new challenges and searching for new knowledges. Good problem-solving analytical ability based on good communication skills. I am very good at working in multicultural groups although I can also do it independently.

COURSES AND CERTIFICATIONS:

System developer Python (Python Advanced, HTML, CSS, JS, Django)	- Lexicon AB	2022 - 2023
Network Administration (Firewall, VPN configuration, VLAN)	- Lexicon AB	2022 -2023
Cloud & Virtualization, Azure, AWS (Azure AD Domain Services, Vmware, Virtualbo	- Lexicon AB	2022 - 2023
Cybersecurity, Pentesting, IDS/IPS, CMD (Kali-linux, Pentesting, PKI)	- Lexicon AB	2022 - 2023
Linux Administration, SQLDB, NO SQLDB (Redhat, Debian, Maria, Mongo)	- Lexicon AB	2022- 2023
Oracle Certified Professional, Oracle AB		- 2004
Interconnecting Cisco Network Devices,		- 2000
Certified UNIX- Linux System Administrator,		- 1996